Morning, roomie.
Hey, you remembered
to put clothes on this morning.
Fifth day's a charm.
Oh...
Oh, Joey, it's so
great to be back here.
I got to tell you,
you're making it so
easy on me and Emma.
Hey, it's great
having you back, you know.
Stay as long as you want.
And when does she
stop crying all night?
Hey, you're not naked.
So, hey, Rach, when will we
expect to see you tonight?
Well, I'll probably be back
to pick her up around 6:00.
But she's in the bedroom
all ready to go.
But she did actually
fall back to sleep, so...
She's probably exhausted
from all that adorable screaming
she did last night.
Well, bye.
Bye.
Hey, I hope Emma isn't
making it too hard on you.
No, hey, it's been great.
Yeah?
Yeah.
And, look, I just
want you to know
that with Rachel staying here
and everything...
all my feelings from before
are totally over, okay?
And even if they weren't,
when you accidentally
walk in
on a woman using
a breast pump...
Yeah, that'll do it.
Wow.
So, uh, how are you?
I'm okay.
Really?
Sure. I mean, do I wish
me and Rachel living together
would have worked out?
Of course.
You know, I'm disappointed,
but it's not like
it's a divorce.
Well, actually...
No, it's not a divorce.
It is not a divorce!
Anyway, I think Rachel
and I need to, you know
get on with our lives.
Maybe... maybe start
seeing other people.
Wow. Really?
Yeah, sure. Why not?
In fact, if you know anyone
that'd be good for me...
Sure, I know lots of girls.
Yeah? Any names come to mind?
Ooh, names?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
Hey. I was just going
to get something to eat.
You want something?
Whatcha got?
Okay, let's see.
We got strained peas.
Strained carrots.
Ooh, strained plums.
We haven't tried that yet.
Goodie!
All right.
Thanks.
Hey... so,
how is it living
with Rachel again?
I mean,
apart from the great food.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
It's just... it's just
weird what's happening
with her and Ross.
You know, yesterday,
he asked me to fix
him up with somebody.
Oh, my God.
Rachel asked me
if I knew anyone
for her, too.
Why are they doing this?
I don't know.
They're so perfect
for each other.
It's crazy.
You know what's crazy,
these jars.
What is it, like
two bites in here?
I just wish they'd realize
they should be together.
I know, I know.
And when they moved
back in together,
I figured, you know,
that's where things
were headed.
I know.
They should be a family.
They should get married
and have more children.
Yes. And they should name
one of their kids Joey.
Tell you what,
I may not have kids.
Someone's got to carry
on the family name.
You know what?
Maybe once they start dating
and they see what's out there,
they'll realize how good
they are for each other.
Yeah, because it is
slim pickin's.
You know, I had this
date last night... yuck!
But we should probably
keep it down.
She's still in the bedroom.
So what are
we going to do?
We just going to go ahead
and set them up with people?
I know. That just
pushes them further
and further apart.
Yeah.
Oh, I know what we can do.
We could set Ross and Rachel up
on horrible dates
so that they'll realize
how good they are together.
Oh, that's a great plan.
Yeah, you know
what the best part of it is?
I get to do my "plan laugh."
( maniacal laughter )
Ooh, yeah...
( both laughing )
Okay, shh... shh...
Not so loud.
We don't want
to wake up, uh...
Hi.
Hey.
You guys aren't doing anything
tonight, are you?
See, now, why would
you assume that?
Just because we're married?
I mean, I will have you know
that we are very hip,
happening people.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to get back to reading
the obituaries.
I was just asking 'cause I need
someone to watch Emma tonight.
Sure, we'll do that.
What are you up to?
Well, Phoebe set me up
on a date.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Why? What's the big deal?
Oh, just figured,
'cause you and Ross are...
What? Slept together
a year and a half ago?
Yeah, I'm all set.
Well, I think it's great
that you're going on a date,
you know?
I mean, it sounds healthy.
I mean, you have needs.
Embrace your womanhood.
You want a job?
Turn off Oprah
and send out a resume.
So, I'll bring her by
around 7:00. Is that okay?
That's perfect.
Oh, you guys are going to have
so much fun.
She's at such a cute age.
Oh, a couple things.
Now that she's eating
solid food,
she poops around the clock.
And watch out for your hair,
'cause she likes to grab at it.
And, oh,
she's also in this phase
where if you leave the room,
she screams bloody murder.
But... thanks, you guys,
have fun.
Suddenly, I wish I was
reading my own name.
Ooh, Joey.
Hey.
I am so excited.
I just set Rachel up
with the worst guy tonight.
All right, who is he?
Well, it's this guy
I used to massage.
And by massage,
I mean, hold down
so he wouldn't turn
over and flash me.
Okay, come here.
Wait till you hear
who I got for Ross.
Oh, yeah.
She's this really
boring woman.
She's a teacher.
A teacher?
Yeah, yeah.
She's really into history
and foreign movies.
Oh, oh, and she
loves puzzles, huh?
Come on,
who loves puzzles?
Well, Ross does.
What... you...
you're ruining the plan.
Joey, you fixed him up
with his perfect woman.
Oh, my God,
you're right.
Yeah.
She even reads
for pleasure.
Oh...
How do you even know
a woman like that?
What? I'm not allowed
to know smart women?
Joey.
I met her at the library.
I went in to pee.
So, now what do we do?
Well, okay,
I'll just call her
and tell her the
date's canceled
and find him
somebody else.
What if we don't find him
somebody else?
We'll just tell her
the date's off,
but we don't tell Ross
and he goes to the restaurant
and gets stood up.
Ooh, I hear that's bad.
Ooh, so this is great.
Rachel's going to have
a terrible date,
Ross gets stood up,
and then they'll realize
how good they have it together.
Ah, yes, the plan.
Ho, ho, ho.
It's not Santa's plan.
No, it's...
( maniacal laughter )
Yeah, you know,
it's not that fun.
No, I think we killed it.
Emma, Emma, look at me.
Well, I think I'll go downstairs
for a while.
( crying )
No, no, no.
No, no, no, it's okay.
It's okay. I didn't go.
Don't cry. It's just a bit.
I'm your Uncle Chandler.
Funny is all I have.
Okay, just so you know,
I'm going to be ovulating
from tomorrow until the sixth.
So, don't touch yourself
in the next 48 hours.
I don't do that.
I'll try to stop.
Wait, did you say
until the sixth?
Yeah.
Today is the sixth.
No, it's not.
Look.
Yeah, see, it's also 2003.
Oh, my God.
Today's the sixth!
I'm nearly done ovulating.
I may have also served
some very questionable meat
at the restaurant.
It's okay, go take the test.
See if we're okay.
Okay.
Hello... lo.
( blubbering )
Tough crib.
Hey, where are all
my ovulation sticks?
There's only one here.
I might have checked to see
if I was ovulating
a couple times.
Chandler...
I am not working.
There's not much
to do around here.
Excuse me, um...
Is there a woman
waiting at the bar?
Um, someone average
height, dark hair,
perhaps doing a puzzle?
Uh, there's a drunk
Chinese guy.
Well, if I'm still
here in an hour,
buy him a drink on me.
Um, can I get you
another glass of wine?
Uh, I don't know
if I should.
I don't want to be
drunk when I...
go home alone tonight.
Got stood up, huh?
Yeah, it's no big deal.
It's just a blind date.
Are you worried your date came,
saw you and left?
No!
We're okay.
I'm still ovulating.
Oh, good, because as of 4:00
this afternoon, I am not.
So, let's do this.
I don't think I can.
Oh, come on.
I know you're not 18 anymore,
but give it a minute.
Because of Emma.
Oh, my God, Emma.
Oh, sweetie, I forgot
you were here.
Oh, you're right,
we can't do this.
We can't leave her alone.
Sorry.
Unless...
Maybe we do it here.
I mean, how much can she
even be aware of at this age?
Well, she's aware
when we leave a room.
She may notice if we start...
canoodling in it.
Canoodling?
Well, I can say hump or screw
in front of the b-a-b-y.
I don't know.
I mean...
I guess having sex in
front of a baby isn't so...
Horrifying?
Scarring?
Something people
go to jail for?
I guess you're right.
You guess I'm right?
When we stayed at that
bed and breakfast,
you wouldn't have sex with me
because you thought a deer
was staring through the window.
Well, what kind
of a sick bastard
wants to do it
in front of deer?
Wow, everything looks
so good.
I think I'm going to have
the chicken.
I-I-I just have to say this:
You're really beautiful.
Oh, well, that's...
that's very sweet.
Thank you.
I'm kind of funny-looking.
What?
Look, I mean, come on,
you're way out of my league.
Everybody in here knows it.
Be that guy over there
is probably saying,
"Ooh, why she out with him?
He must be rich."
Well, I'm not.
( nervous laughter )
So, what do you think
you want to order?
I'm real excited
about that chicken.
I'm not funny, either.
So, if you were thinking
well, he's not
that good-looking,
but maybe we'll
have some laughs.
That ain't gonna happen.
Well, come on, Steve,
let's not rule out
nervous laughter.
Hey, now, wait a minute.
Phoebe told me that you owned
your own restaurant.
That's impressive.
I lost it... to drugs.
I silk-screen
T-shirts now.
Really?
What's that like?
It's really fulfilling doing
something you hate for no money.
That's right.
I have no money,
I'm not funny, I live
in a studio apartment,
with two other guys,
and I'm pretty sure
I'm infertile.
Now, come on,
come on, Steve.
There must be something
that you like about yourself.
I do like my hair.
Really?
I mean... I...
Hello.
Phoebe, it's me.
I'm going to hunt you down
and kill you.
Hey, Rach.
This is the worst date ever.
How could you set me up
with this creep?
You know you are talking
about one of my dear,
dear friends.
I don't care.
This guy is a nightmare.
All right, so he gets a little
crazy when he's stoned.
He's not stoned.
Did he go out for a cigarette?
Yeah, four times.
My dear sweet Rach.
Well, our plan
is working.
Rachel's having
a miserable time,
and Ross is just stood up
somewhere
at a restaurant
all alone.
Oh, great. Pretty soon
they'll be back together.
By the time anyone's figured out
what we've done,
we'll be in sunny Mexico.
Oh, wait, that's the end
of a different plan.
Oh, she's asleep.
Chandler.
What are you doing?
Emma was doing it.
She's asleep.
Ooh. If she's asleep,
that means we can...
Yes.
But we have to be fast.
Oh, okay, I'll try.
And you can't make
any noise.
Okay, I'll try.
Hello.
Emma?
Hey.
Hi.
How are you?
Where are
your baby-sitters, huh?
Why's the bedroom door closed?
You can't have S-E-X
when you're taking care
of the B-A-B-I-E.
I've got bad news.
The Chinese guy left.
If was meant to be,
it's meant to be.
Look, you got stood up.
Who cares?
We're going to show you
a good time.
Sit and relax.
In fact, let me bring you
a crab cake appetizer
on the house.
Wow, free crab cakes.
Well, that's nice.
Although, I was hoping
to have sex tonight.
Ooh.
Just the crab cakes.
What are
you doing?
Are you trying
to get him to stay?
Because you
can't do that.
Just get out
of here, okay?
What's... what's going on?
Uh, okay, um...
The waiters have
a little pool going.
We have a bet on how long
it will take
before you...
give up and go home.
What?!
You... you're making money
off my misery?
Well, if you stay
till 9:20 I am.
This is unbelievable.
I have never been so insulted
in my life.
Now if you'll wrap up
my free crab cakes,
I'll be on my way.
Well, that was weird.
You were loud,
and I was fast.
I think we may have
really done it this time.
I wish I didn't have
to wait to take a
pregnancy test.
You might want to get
some more of those, too.
Where's Emma?
Oh, my God,
where's Emma?
Where's Emma?!
Don't ask me.
I was in there canoodling you.
Okay, okay, I'm sure
that Rachel came home early
and picked up Emma.
You go look
across the hall,
and I'll call her cell.
Okay.
You better hope
that we're pregnant.
Because one way or another,
we're giving a baby
back to Rachel.
( sobbing ):
I can't believe
I'm crying in front of you.
You must think
I'm so pathetic.
No, no, no.
I admire a man who can cry.
Really?
Don't touch
my coat!
( phone ringing )
Oh, sorry.
That's my phone.
Hello.
Hey, Rach, how's it going?
Oh, God, this is
the worst date ever.
( loud sob )
Oh, come on...
Look, you know what,
I'm sorry,
but did you really think
that this was going well?
What's up?
Hey, did you stop by here?
No.
Oh, my God!
Oh, thank God.
Emma, there you are!
What... what do you mean
"there you are"?
Where was she?
Oh, we were playing
peek-a-boo.
She loves it when
I'm dramatic.
What...?
Why the hell
did you take her?
Because you two were
having sex.
No, we weren't.
Don't you lie to me.
I can tell by Chandler's hair.
You are so lazy.
Can't you get on top for once?
All right, all right.
We were... we were
trying to make a baby.
Monica's ovulating.
It is unacceptable
that you two would have sex
with Emma in the next room.
And I'm going to have
to tell Rachel about it.
No, no, no.
No, please don't.
Joey, she will kill us.
Hey, I gotta.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless you name your firstborn
child Joey.
What? Why?
Hey, I may never have kids
and somebody's got to carry on
my family name.
Your family name
is Tribbiani.
Oh, you almost had me.
Look...
I think I know the answer
to this question, but...
Would you like
to make love to me?
Really, really not.
Oh, it's just as well.
Doesn't work anyway.
All right, well,
that's good to know.
Good night, Steve.
( shudders and groans )
Hey, what's wrong?
I just had a rough night.
Oh, crab cake?
Ew!
So what happened?
Oh, well, I...
it's kind of weird
to talk to you
about this, but...
Monica told me
you had a blind date.
Yeah.
I did, too.
Oh.
But it is it
technically a date
if the other
person doesn't show up?
Oh, oh, no.
Do you think she walked in,
saw you and left?
Why does everyone
keep saying that?
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
I wish my date hadn't shown up.
That bad?
Well, he makes T-shirts
for a living,
and he thought it would
be appropriate
to give me... this.
Female Body Inspector?
What size is that?
Now, wait a minute.
So they're going to name
their first child Joey?
Uh-huh.
How do I get them
to name the next
one after me?
It's easy.
You just walk
in on them having sex.
Oh, so they owe me
like three Phoebes.
Oh, my God!
Look. It's Ross and Rachel.
Oh, the plan is working.
( maniacal laughter )
Don't do the plan laugh.
The first dates
we've had in months,
and they were both
such disasters.
Huh.
You know, it is weird
that Phoebe would set me up
on a date that was awful,
on the same night
that Joey set you up
on a date that didn't
even show.
Wait a minute.
You don't think
it was intentional?
I mean, that's
just stupid.
We're geniuses.
Look at 'em.
They're really bonding.
Oh, yeah. They're falling
in love all over again.
Oh, they see us.
Oh, they look mad.
Oh, they figured it out.
They're coming
this way. Run.
Where?
Mexico!
Can you believe
they're still not here?
I know.
A double blind date
and we both get stood up.
What are the chances?
I know. I'm so bummed.
Could we have our
free crab cakes now?
What?
We've been stood up,
and we want
our free crab cakes.
Guys, give it a rest.
Nobody's betting
on you tonight.
Although we do have
a pool going
to see how long it takes
that guy to cry.
I have such fat hands!
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org